[
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-A0136",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following technologies will enable you to install networking devices that need power to function, in a location that has no power outlets?",
        "choices": [
            "EoP",
            "PoE",
            "WAP",
            "Hub"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Power over Ethernet (PoE) enables placement of equipment in areas that otherwise would not be able to accept it. Only four of the eight wires in twisted pair wiring are used for communication. The power is sent over the wires that are not used in communication. If the devices on both ends don't support PoE, then an injector can be used to add power to the line on the way to its destination. Compatibility is important, and there are limits to the amount of power that can be transmitted this way. Ethernet over Power (EoP) is not in the CompTIA A+ objectives, but it uses special devices to send Ethernet communications over existing wiring such as in a household. A wireless access point (WAP) is a device that is used to connect wireless devices to a wired network or to each other. Some WAPs support PoE. A hub is a very simple network connectivity device",
        "topic": [
            "Networking"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-A0138",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You are installing network cabling in a drop ceiling of an office space. The ceiling area is used to circulate breathable air. What type of cable must you install?",
        "choices": [
            "Coaxial",
            "UTP",
            "Fiber-optic",
            "Plenum"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "The cable can be any of the three major types, coaxial, twisted pair, or fiber, but it needs to be plenum rated. Normal cables have a PVC coating, which produces a poisonous gas when burned. Plenum-rated cables have a Teflon coating, which is not toxic when burned",
        "topic": [
            "Networking"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-A0139",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You need to install a wireless access point in a drop ceiling where there is no access to a power source. Which technology will allow you to get power to that device?",
        "choices": [
            "EoP",
            "PoE",
            "Hub",
            "Repeater/extender"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Power over Ethernet (PoE) allows you to power an Ethernet device (such as a switch) through one of the Ethernet ports. For it to work, the access point and the device it plugs into both need to support PoE. Further, both the access point and device need to be compatible with each other. EoP, while not on the current A+ objectives, is a technology that allows the user to transmit Ethernet signals over existing power lines. This can be useful in a place where running Ethernet wires is impossible, but more often Wi-Fi is used in those situations instead. A hub can be used to regenerate a signal, but they also need a power source and are not a wireless access point. A repeater/extender is essentially the same as a hub. It requires power to regenerate a signal and send it on its way",
        "topic": [
            "Networking"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-A0528",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You are having problems printing to a networked printer from your Windows workstation. Several jobs were sent, but none printed. You just tried to print a test page and nothing came out. What should you do?",
        "choices": [
            "Check your connections and stop and restart the print spooler.",
            "Turn the printer off and back on.",
            "Use the printer's display to clear out the oldest job, take it offline, and put it back online.",
            "Press the Reset button on the printer."
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "If your printer isn't spitting out print jobs, it may be a good idea to print a test page and see whether that works. The test page information is stored in the printer's memory, so there's no formatting or translating of jobs required. If the test page works, then the problem is not communication between PC and printer. If nothing happens, double-check your connections and stop and restart the print spooler. If garbage prints, there is likely a problem with the printer or the print driver",
        "topic": [
            "Hardware and Network Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-A0552",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You have sent several print jobs to a networked printer and nothing has printed. You do not have printer administrator access. What can you do to see whether your Windows computer is communicating properly with the printer?",
        "choices": [
            "Send the print job in RAW format.",
            "Stop and restart the print spooler.",
            "Print a test page.",
            "Print a blank document from Notepad."
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "If your printer isn't spitting out print jobs, it may be a good idea to print a test page and see whether that works. The test page information is stored in the printer's memory, so there's no formatting or translating of jobs required. It's simply a test to make sure that your printer hears your computer. If the test page works but other print jobs don't print, there could be a problem with the application or the driver",
        "topic": [
            "Hardware and Network Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-A0584",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You have been told to configure a static IP of `110.110.1.5` for a server. This server will need to be able to access the Internet. Which one of the following is not a required setting to configure?",
        "choices": [
            "Default gateway",
            "IP address",
            "Proxy server",
            "Subnet mask"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "An IP address on a device can be either dynamic or static. In a static IP address, the minimum amount of information that needs to be configured is the IP address, subnet mask, and, if the computer will access the Internet or other networks, a default gateway. A proxy server is an added security measure between a device and the Internet. It is used to translate between protocols and filter out certain types of traffic such as keeping inappropriate websites out and confidential data in the network",
        "topic": [
            "Operating Systems"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-A0681",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You need to configure a virtual private network (VPN) for an employee working remotely on a Windows Pro computer. What category group in Windows Settings provides options for establishing dial-up or VPN connections?",
        "choices": [
            "Network and Sharing Center",
            "Network & Internet",
            "System",
            "Accounts"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Network & Internet is the Settings category that provides options for setting up VPN or dial-up connections. Network and Sharing Center is a Control Panel utility. The System category of Settings deals with display, sound, power, notification, and other settings. The Accounts category is useful for managing users and syncing settings. In Windows 11, but not Windows 10, Windows Backup is included in the Accounts category",
        "topic": [
            "Operating Systems"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-A1106",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You have a small office with frequent visitors and want to provide a separate VLAN to segregate the visitor traffic from your network traffic for security reasons. What is the minimum connectivity device needed to accomplish this?",
        "choices": [
            "Hub",
            "Bridge",
            "Managed switch",
            "Unmanaged switch"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "To segregate a local area network (LAN) into two virtual LANs (VLANs), you would need a managed switch. Managed switches contain software that allows for port configuration, diagnostics, and monitoring situations such as port flapping. An unmanaged switch is simply a connectivity device. It can't be used to segregate ports into separate VLANs. A bridge is used to aggregate two or more networks into one. A hub is simply a connectivity device that is a single collision domain, whereas each port on a switch (managed or not) is its own collision domain. Hubs are seldom found on networks now, but they are often used to provide multiple ports for a single connection on a computer such as a USB port. Note that some routers have the ability to create a VLAN by using different IP address ranges, but more often a switch is used",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9781119862642/c10.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-A1136",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following is not true about DNS servers?",
        "choices": [
            "They translate IP addresses to domain names like `[Sybex.com](http://sybex.com)`.",
            "AAAA DNS records identify IPv6 addresses.",
            "A records identify IPv4 addresses.",
            "There is a setting in IP configuration to identify the DNS server to use."
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Domain Name Service (DNS) servers reconcile human friendly names like `Sybex.com` to IP addresses so that a browser can find them (not IP address to domain name). A DNS server can be configured on a client computer automatically by a DHCP server, or manually on the Networking tab of a network connection by clicking on either IPv4 or IPv6 properties. DNS differentiates between IPv4 and IPv6 by identifying IPv6 addresses as AAAA records and IPv4 addresses as A records",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9781119862642/c10.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-B0020",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "For IPv6, which of the following statements are true? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "Each IPv6 interface can have only one address.",
            "Each IPv6 interface is required to have a link-local address.",
            "IPv6 addresses are incompatible with IPv4 networks.",
            "IPv6 does not use broadcasts."
        ],
        "answer": "B,D",
        "solution": "Each IPv6 interface can and often does have multiple addresses assigned to it. IPv6 is backward compatible with IPv4 by using tunneling, dual stack, or translation. IPv6 uses multicast addresses in place of broadcast addresses, and a link-local address is established either automatically when a computer boots up or by manually configuring it, but either way the link-local address must be present",
        "topic": [
            "Networking"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-B0115",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "You've been asked to help with a network for a company that has 50 computers. They've been using workgroups, but it is getting too difficult. There is an assortment of Windows editions on the computers, including Windows Home, Windows Pro, and Windows Pro for Workstations. What will you do to set up their new network? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "Upgrade all the Windows Home PCs to Windows Pro.",
            "Install a server with Active Directory.",
            "Downgrade all the Windows Pro for Workstations to Windows Pro.",
            "Upgrade all the workstations to Windows Enterprise."
        ],
        "answer": "A,B",
        "solution": "A network with that many computers (typically more than 10) needs a domain for security management. The Windows Home edition PCs can't log into a domain, so they would need to be upgraded to at least the Pro edition. It's not necessary to upgrade them to Pro for Workstations or Enterprise editions",
        "topic": [
            "Operating Systems"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862642-B0177",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "An iPad user reports that when they are in a certain part of the building, their wireless connection intermittently drops. What are the two most likely causes of this? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "Poor wireless buffering in the iPad",
            "Interference with the wireless signal",
            "Weak signal strength from the wireless access point",
            "Retracted Wi-Fi antenna on the iPad"
        ],
        "answer": "B,C",
        "solution": "There are a number of reasons intermittent wireless connections can occur, but the two most common are lack of a good signal and interference. Increasing the number of wireless access points, or being closer to one, can address the lack of a good signal. Interference can be addressed by reducing the number of devices competing for the same channel or by moving away from walls or obstacles. A poor wireless signal can cause video buffering, not the other way around, and Wi-Fi antennas for mobile devices are often found inside the display housing, not a retractable antenna",
        "topic": [
            "Software Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862642/c08.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862918-A0076",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What devices transfer packets across multiple networks and use tables to store network addresses to determine the best destination?",
        "choices": [
            "Routers",
            "Firewalls",
            "Hubs",
            "Switches"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Routers are designed to route (transfer) packets across networks. They are able to do this routing, determining the best path to take, based on the internal routing tables that they maintain",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862918/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119862918-A0086",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following devices works with MAC addresses to determine what to do with network traffic?",
        "choices": [
            "Hub",
            "Router",
            "Patch panel",
            "Switch"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "A switch is a Layer 2 device; therefore, it works with hardware (MAC) addresses. Hubs and patch panels work at Layer 1 and deal with bits, and routers work at Layer 3 and work with logical IP addresses",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119862918/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137658237-A0066",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following is the most important piece of information needed to connect to a specific wireless network?",
        "choices": [
            "Channel",
            "MAC address",
            "SSID",
            "Administrator password"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "**Explanation:** The service set identifier (SSID) is the most important piece of information required to connect to a wireless network; it is the name of the wireless network.\n\n **Incorrect answers:** The wireless channel number isn’t necessarily needed as the wireless access point (WAP) might autonegotiate the channel. Also, MAC address filtering is not enabled by default, so the MAC address might not be needed. (In fact, the admin would enter this at the WAP, not from the client computer.) You need the administrator password only if you want to make configuration changes to the wireless access point. For example, if you want to implement MAC filtering, you have to log in to the WAP with an admin password to configure it",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9780137658237/ch02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137658237-A0173",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "A user recently purchased a new wireless 802.11ac router. After connecting a laptop with an 802.11ac wireless adapter to the wireless network, he notices that the signal strength on the laptop is poor, and the laptop only connects at 300 Mbps. The user moves the laptop nearer the WAP but is still experiencing the same issue. Which of the following is most likely the cause?",
        "choices": [
            "The cable modem is faulty.",
            "The laptop is connecting to the incorrect wireless network.",
            "The router’s wireless card drivers are faulty.",
            "The wireless antennas on the router need to be replaced."
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "**Explanation:** The laptop is probably connecting to a different wireless network, either in the home next door or in an adjacent business—and that network does not have encryption, it would seem. Based on the speed—300 Mbps—you can safely assume that the connection being made is to an 802.11n network (or something similar). The best course of action is to verify the SSID name of the 802.11ac router, forget the current wireless network, and connect to the new network. You might find that in some cases a laptop connects at a slower speed (such as 802.11n), even though faster speeds (such as 802.11ac and 802.11ax) are available. The reason could be due to the configuration of the WAP or the wireless adapter on the laptop. That’s not one of the listed answers and is not the case here because of the poor signal strength mentioned in the scenario.\n\n **Incorrect answers:** The cable modem isn’t part of the equation in this scenario. You are only interested in connecting to the wireless network to start. A router (wireless access point) doesn’t have a wireless card like the ones in desktops and laptops. Also, you don’t know whether the device is faulty yet because the laptop never connected to it. The same goes for the wireless antennas",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9780137658237/ch04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137658237-A0190",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "A customer has a home office. Which of the following technologies would benefit from the use of QoS?",
        "choices": [
            "SSID",
            "Instant messaging",
            "Email",
            "VoIP"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "**Explanation:** Voice over IP (VoIP) is a streaming telephony application. Streaming applications such as VoIP and online games can benefit from QoS. QoS stands for quality of service, which is the capability to provide different priorities to different applications (or computers). It guarantees network bandwidth for real-time streaming of media applications such as VoIP. But always check whether the customer’s Internet connection has the required bandwidth. For example, a typical 4K video stream requires 25 Mbps.\n\n **Incorrect answers:** The SSID is the name or identifier of a wireless network. Instant messaging and email are not streaming applications; therefore, they would not benefit from the use of QoS",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9780137658237/ch04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137658237-B0012",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "A laptop cannot access the wireless network. Which of the following statements best describe the most likely causes of this? (Select the two best answers.)",
        "choices": [
            "The function key for wireless was pressed by accident.",
            "The user installed a new web browser.",
            "The wireless network was forgotten in Windows.",
            "The computer is obtaining an IP address automatically."
        ],
        "answer": "A,C",
        "solution": "**Explanation:** Most laptops have a special function key (for example, F12) that allows you to enable or disable the Wi-Fi connection with a single key press. Also, a wireless network can be “forgotten” in the operating system. If this happens, the laptop has to be reconnected to the wireless network.\n\n **Incorrect answers:** After you are connected to a network, you can typically use whatever web browser you want, as long as the browser is compatible with the operating system that is in use. Client computers (such as laptops) normally obtain their IP addresses automatically from a DHCP server, so this is not a likely problem",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9780137658237/ch02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137658237-B0038",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "A customer tells you that a networked printer is not printing documents. You successfully ping the printer’s IP address. Which of the following is the most likely cause of this problem? (Select the two best answers.)",
        "choices": [
            "The printer is low on toner.",
            "The network cable is unplugged.",
            "The printer is out of paper.",
            "The gateway address on the printer is incorrect.",
            "The spooler is not functioning."
        ],
        "answer": "C,E",
        "solution": "**Explanation:** The printer could simply be out of paper, or the spooler could be malfunctioning. If the printer is out of paper, fill all trays and suggest that the user check the trays every couple days or so. If the spooler is not functioning, you should restart the spooler service in the Services console window or in the Command Prompt with the **net stop spooler** and **net start spooler** commands.\n\n **Incorrect answers:** If the printer were low on toner, you would get weak print or completely blank pages. If the network cable were unplugged, you wouldn’t be able to ping the printer. Printers don’t always use gateway addresses, but if this one did, it wouldn’t affect your ability to connect to it (as long as it was on the LAN). The gateway address is used so that the printer can communicate with computers beyond the LAN",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9780137658237/ch04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0003",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which layer of the Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) model is responsible for the logical addressing of end systems and the routing of datagrams on a network?",
        "choices": [
            "Physical",
            "Data link",
            "Network",
            "Transport",
            "Session",
            "Presentation",
            "Application"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Network layer protocols (such as IP) contain headers that specify logical addresses for end system communication and route datagrams across a network. The physical layer defines standards for physical and mechanical characteristics of a network. The data link layer uses media access control (MAC) or hardware addresses, not logical addresses. The transport layer uses port numbers, not logical addresses. Session layer protocols create and maintain a dialogue between end systems. Presentation layer protocols are responsible for the formatting, translation, and presentation of information. The application layer provides an entry point for applications to access the protocol stack and prepare information for transmission across a network",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0004",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What layer of the Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) model is responsible for translating and formatting information?",
        "choices": [
            "Physical",
            "Data link",
            "Network",
            "Transport",
            "Session",
            "Presentation",
            "Application"
        ],
        "answer": "F",
        "solution": "The presentation layer implements functions that provide formatting, translation, and presentation of information. No other layers of the OSI model translate and format application data",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0005",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following devices typically operates at the network layer of the Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) model?",
        "choices": [
            "Proxy server",
            "Hub",
            "Network interface adapter",
            "Router"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "A router connects networks at the network layer of the OSI model. Proxy servers operate at the application layer. Network interface adapters operate at both the data link and the physical layers. Hubs are physical layer devices",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0008",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "At which layer of the Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) model are there TCP/IP protocols than can provide either connectionless or connection-oriented services to applications?",
        "choices": [
            "Physical",
            "Data link",
            "Network",
            "Transport",
            "Session",
            "Presentation",
            "Application"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "There are two types of transport layer protocols: connection-oriented and connectionless. Connection-oriented protocols guarantee the delivery of data from source to destination by creating a connection between the sender and the receiver before any data is transmitted. Connectionless protocols do not require a connection between end systems in order to pass data. The physical layer does not use connectionless or connection-oriented protocols; it defines standards for transmitting and receiving information over a network. The data link layer provides physical addressing and final packaging of data for transmission. The network layer is responsible for logical addressing and routing. The session layer is responsible for creating and maintaining a dialogue between end systems. The presentation layer is responsible for the formatting, translation, and presentation of information. The application layer provides an entry point for applications to access the protocol stack and prepare information for transmission across a network",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0021",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the OSI model layers is responsible for syntax translation and compression or encryption?",
        "choices": [
            "Data link",
            "Network",
            "Session",
            "Presentation",
            "Application"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "The presentation layer provides a syntax translation service that enables two computers to communicate, despite their use of different bit-encoding methods. This translation service also enables systems using compressed or encrypted data to communicate with each other",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0025",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which layer of the Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) model would be responsible for converting a text file encoded using EBCDIC on the sending system into ASCII code, when required by the receiving system?",
        "choices": [
            "Application",
            "Presentation",
            "Session",
            "Physical"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "The presentation layer of the OSI model is responsible for translating different kinds of syntax, including text-encoding systems, such as EBCDIC and ASCII. The application, session, and physical layers do not perform this function",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0090",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following statements explains the purpose of the twists in twisted pair cabling?",
        "choices": [
            "The twists prevent collisions.",
            "The twists completely eliminate crosstalk and electromagnetic interference (EMI) in adjacent wire pairs.",
            "The twists prevent crosstalk in adjacent wire pairs and limit the effects of EMI on the signals carried over the cable.",
            "The twists extend the bend radius allowance of the cable."
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "The twists in a twisted pair cable prevent the signals on the different wires from interfering with each other (which is called crosstalk) and also provide resistance to outside electromagnetic interference. The twists have no effect on collisions. The twists cannot completely eliminate the effects of EMI. Twists have nothing to do with the bend radius allowance for the cable",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0207",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following protocols is not used for Storage Area Networks (SANs)?",
        "choices": [
            "iSCSI",
            "FCoE",
            "VoIP",
            "Fibre Channel"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) is a technology for the transmission of voice communications over IP networks; it is not a SAN protocol. Internet Small Computer Systems Interface (iSCSI), Fibre Channel over Ethernet (FCoE), and Fibre Channel are all SAN protocols",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0212",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following Storage Area Network (SAN) technologies is primarily used by supercomputers as a high-speed, low-latency connection between Central Processing Units (CPUs) and storage systems?",
        "choices": [
            "InfiniBand",
            "Fibre Channel",
            "iSCSI",
            "FCoE"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "InfiniBand is a high-end storage infrastructure technology that provides data transfer rates of up to 2.5 Gbps and scalable support for up to 64,000 devices. It is primarily used in high performance computing environments to replace older bus technologies connecting CPUs to storage arrays. Fibre Channel, Internet Small Computer System Interface (iSCSI), and Fibre Channel over Ethernet (FCoE) are all SAN technologies, but they are more commonly used in Local Area Network (LAN) environments",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0217",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following protocols uses jumbo frames to increase performance levels on storage area networks?",
        "choices": [
            "Ethernet",
            "IP",
            "Fibre Channel",
            "iSCSI"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Ethernet uses jumbo frames to transfer large amounts of data more efficiently. On a packet-switched network, each packet requires header data, which adds to the network's transmission overhead. Splitting large files into a great many small packets can lead to so much overhead that network efficiency is impaired. Ethernet typically restricts frame size to 1500 bytes, but jumbo frames enable Ethernet systems to create frames up to 9000 bytes. Frames are data link layer protocol data units, so Internet Protocol (IP), operating at the network layer, is not involved in creating them. Fibre Channel and iSCSI are specialized storage area networking protocols that do not use jumbo frames",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0251",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Small Office Home Office (SOHO) networks typically use a multifunction connectivity device that can perform all but which one of the following functions?",
        "choices": [
            "DHCP",
            "DNS",
            "Switch",
            "Router",
            "Hub",
            "NAT router",
            "Access Point (AP)"
        ],
        "answer": "E",
        "solution": "SOHO multifunction devices typically function as routers connecting the local network to an Internet Service Provider (ISP), switches providing wired connections to host devices, Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol (DHCP) servers assigning IP addresses, Domain Name System (DNS) servers resolving names into IP addresses, Network Address Translation (NAT) routers providing hosts with private IP addresses access to the Internet, and APs providing wireless devices with access to the network. They do not function as hubs",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0255",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Virtual Local Area Networks (VLANs) create the administrative boundaries on a switched network that are otherwise provided by which of the following devices?",
        "choices": [
            "Hubs",
            "Routers",
            "Firewalls",
            "Bridges"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Connecting subnets with routers at the network layer maintains the data link layer administrative boundaries that prevent broadcast transmissions from being propagated throughout the entire internetwork. Switching eliminates those data link layer boundaries, and administrators can use VLANs to simulate them. Because hubs propagate all of the traffic they receive out through all of their ports indiscriminately, they create no administrative boundaries. Firewalls are filtering devices that protect networks against malicious traffic; their functions are not related to VLANs. Switches are essentially multiport bridges that forward incoming traffic only to the device for which it is destined. Therefore, bridges are more closely related to eliminating administrative boundaries than to establishing them",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0257",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following is another term for a multiport bridge?",
        "choices": [
            "Router",
            "Switch",
            "Hub",
            "Gateway"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "A switch is a data link layer device that essentially performs the function of a bridge for each device connected to one of its ports. It can therefore be described as a multiport bridge. Routers, hubs, and gateways are devices that operate at the network, physical, and application layers, respectively, so they cannot be described as bridges",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0258",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following devices enables two computers to communicate when they are using different protocols at each layer of the Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) reference model?",
        "choices": [
            "A router",
            "A switch",
            "A hub",
            "A gateway"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "A gateway enables two devices using different protocols to communicate by performing translation and conversion services for them. Routers, hubs, and switches all require the same protocol at some of the OSI model layers",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0259",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Ralph is installing an Ethernet Local Area Network (LAN) for a small business with two offices on opposite sides of a courtyard. Ralph plans to run a multimode fiber-optic cable across the courtyard, but the budget is limited, and he cannot use fiber for the whole network. Therefore, he installs Unshielded Twisted Pair (UTP) cable in the two offices, which have 10 and 12 workstations, respectively. Which of the following devices should Ralph use to join the two UTP installations together into one LAN using the fiber-optic run across the courtyard, while keeping the cost to a minimum?",
        "choices": [
            "Media converters",
            "Hubs",
            "Switches",
            "Routers"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Media converters will enable Ralph to join the multimode fiber-optic run to the UTP at both sides of the courtyard while maintaining a single network at minimum cost. Inexpensive small-business hubs and switches cannot join different media together. Routers can join different media, but they are more expensive, and they would separate the installation into three separate networks",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0269",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following statements about hubs is not true?",
        "choices": [
            "Hubs are data link layer devices that connect network devices in a star or ring topology.",
            "Hubs amplify and repeat signals received through one port out all other ports regardless of the destination.",
            "Hubs are physical layer devices that connect network devices in a star topology.",
            "Hubs provide internal crossover circuits and use uplink ports to form a hierarchical star."
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Hubs are physical layer devices that amplify and repeat signals out all ports except the one through which the data was received, regardless of the destination. Hubs are used to physically connect end systems to a star topology. Hubs typically provide an internal crossover circuit connection. Uplink ports are used to extend the distance of a star network, forming a hierarchical star",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0290",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following network devices does not employ Access Control Lists (ACLs) to restrict access?",
        "choices": [
            "Routers",
            "Hubs",
            "Switches",
            "Wireless Access Points (WAPs)"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "ACLs restrict access to network devices by filtering usernames, MAC addresses, IP addresses, or other criteria. Routers, switches, and WAPs all use ACLs to control access to them. Hubs are purely physical layer devices that relay electrical or optical signals. They have no way of controlling access to them",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0318",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "VLANs create the administrative boundaries on a switched network that are otherwise provided by which of the following devices?",
        "choices": [
            "Hubs",
            "Routers",
            "Domains",
            "Bridges"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Connecting subnets with routers at the network layer maintains the data link layer administrative boundaries that prevent broadcast transmissions from being propagated throughout the entire internetwork. Switching eliminates those data link layer boundaries, and administrators can use Virtual Local Area Networks (VLANs) to simulate them. Because hubs propagate all of the traffic they receive out through all of their ports indiscriminately, they create no administrative boundaries. Domains are logical groups of network devices defined by the Domain Name System (DNS). Their functions are not related to VLANs in any way. Switches are essentially multiport bridges that forward incoming traffic only to the device for which it is destined. Therefore, bridges are more closely related to eliminating administrative boundaries than to establishing them",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0328",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following Power over Ethernet (PoE) specifications supplies power to devices using the spare wire pair on a 10Base-T or 100Base-TX twisted pair network?",
        "choices": [
            "Alternative A",
            "Alternative B",
            "4PPoE",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "The Alternative B PoE variant can use the spare wire pair in a CAT 5 or better 10Base-T or 100Base-TX cable to supply power to connected devices. The Alternative A and 4PPoE variants cannot use the spare wire pair in this manner; they supply power using the wire pairs that carry data at the same time. For Gigabit Ethernet or faster installations, Alternative B is also capable of using the data wire pairs",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0396",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "When a service fails to start on a Windows server, an entry is typically created in which of the following event logs?",
        "choices": [
            "Application",
            "Security",
            "Setup",
            "System"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "On a Windows system, information about services, including successful service starts and failures, is recorded in the System event log. The Application, Security, and Setup logs typically do not contain this type of information",
        "topic": [
            "Network Operations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0399",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following event logs on a Windows server can record information about both successful and failed access attempts?",
        "choices": [
            "System",
            "Application",
            "Security",
            "Setup"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "When you enable audit policies on Windows systems, you can specify whether to audit successful or failed events (or both), including access attempts. This audit information is recorded in the Security event log. The System, Application, and Setup events logs typically do not record both successful and failed access attempts",
        "topic": [
            "Network Operations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0405",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a type of error typically found in network interface statistics?",
        "choices": [
            "Runt",
            "Encapsulation",
            "Giant",
            "CRC",
            "Jumbo"
        ],
        "answer": "E",
        "solution": "Jumbo frames is a feature supported by some Ethernet implementations that enable frames to exceed the 1500-byte maximum data payload defined in the IEEE 802.3 standard. Runt frames, giant frames, Cyclical Redundancy Check (CRC) errors, and encapsulation errors are all types of errors typically reported in network interface diagnostics",
        "topic": [
            "Network Operations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0477",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following best describes the difference between cold, warm, and hot backup sites?",
        "choices": [
            "Whether the backup site is owned, borrowed, or rented",
            "The age of the most recent backup stored at the site",
            "The cost of the hardware used at the site",
            "The time needed to get the site up and running"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "Cold, warm, and hot backup sites are a disaster recovery mechanism that enables a network to be activated at a remote location when a catastrophe occurs. The temperature refers to the sites readiness to assume the role of the network. A cold site is just a space at a remote location. The hardware and software must be procured and installed before the network can be restored. A warm site has hardware in place that must be installed and configured. It takes less time to restore the network than at a cold site, but more than at a hot site. A hot site has all of the necessary hardware installed and configured. The network can go live as soon as the most recent data is restored",
        "topic": [
            "Network Operations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0492",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following is the most commonly recommended fire suppression system for a datacenter?",
        "choices": [
            "Carbon Dioxide",
            "Water",
            "Foam",
            "HFC-125"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "Hydrofluorocarbon (HFC) 125 is a heat-absorbing gas that is frequently used for fire suppression systems. Many large datacenters include HFC-125 total flooding fire suppression systems because the products resulting from the flame retardation process are less toxic than carbon dioxide and do not damage electric and electronic equipment as water and foam do",
        "topic": [
            "Network Operations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0656",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Alice is working the help desk when a user calls and reports that she is unable to connect to the Internet. Which of the following steps is the one Alice is least likely to perform first when troubleshooting the problem?",
        "choices": [
            "Check the configuration of the router connecting the LAN to the Internet",
            "Ask the user if she can access resources on the local network",
            "Check to see if anyone else is experiencing the same problem",
            "Check the user's job title to see if she is an important person in the company"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "There are many possible causes for the problem that are more likely than a router configuration error, so this is not something Alice would check first. Asking if the user can access the local network attempts to isolate the problem. If she cannot, the problem could be in her computer; if she can, then the problem lies somewhere in the Internet access infrastructure. If other users are experiencing the problem, then the issue should receive a higher priority, and Alice knows that the problem does not lie in the user's computer. While it might not be the first thing she checks, it is a political reality that higher ranking users often get preferential treatment",
        "topic": [
            "Network Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0785",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Alice is examining a captured sample of network traffic to create a network performance baseline for future reference. She notices that the sample contains a flood of multicast traffic, but she does not know why. After some investigation, she learns that there is video traffic on the network being transmitted as multicasts, but it is only intended for a particular group of users, not for everyone. However, since the multicast traffic is flooding the network, all of the hosts must process the packets, possibly resulting in performance degradation or even Denial-of-Service (DoS). Which of the following can Alice use to prevent the traffic from being processed by the unintended hosts?",
        "choices": [
            "Asymmetric routing",
            "Flow control",
            "Multipathing",
            "IGMP snooping"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP) snooping is a switching technique that prevents network hosts from receiving multicast packets when they are not members of the multicast group. The multicast traffic will still appear on the network, but only the members of the multicast group will process the packets. Asymmetric routing and multipathing all affect the route that the packets take through the network, and flow control only affects the speed at which transmitting systems send packets. None of these can control which hosts process the incoming packets",
        "topic": [
            "Network Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0854",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You are a network administrator attempting to use your workstation on the internal network to remotely control a web server called WebServ1 on the perimeter network. However, the remote desktop client software is unable to establish a connection to the server. You can see all the computers on your local network and on the perimeter network. You try using the `ping` utility to test the TCP/IP functionality of WebServ1, and the `ping` test is successful. You then call your colleague on the same internal network and have her try to connect to WebServ1 using the same remote access tool. She connects to WebServ1 successfully. Which of the following could be the cause of the problem you are experiencing?",
        "choices": [
            "Blocked TCP/UDP ports on the web server",
            "Name resolution failure",
            "Incorrect firewall settings on your workstation",
            "Unresponsive service on the web server"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Because your colleague can connect to WebServ1 successfully, the problem is not an unresponsive service or blocked ports on the server. The problem is not a name resolution failure, because you can successfully ping WebServ1 by name. Therefore, of the options listed, the only possible problem must be that the firewall on your workstation is configured to block the remote desktop client's traffic",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9781119807308/c06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0861",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which layer of the Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) model has its own logical addressing system and is responsible for routing packets from one network to another?",
        "choices": [
            "Physical",
            "Data link",
            "Network",
            "Transport",
            "Session",
            "Presentation",
            "Application"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Network layer protocols specify logical addresses, such as IP addresses, for end system communication. They also use those addresses to route packets to destinations on other networks. The physical layer defines standards for physical and mechanical characteristics of a network. The data link layer uses Media Access Control (MAC) or hardware addresses, not logical addresses. The transport layer uses port numbers, not logical addresses. Session layer protocols create and maintain a dialog between end systems. Presentation layer protocols are responsible for the formatting, translation, and presentation of information. The application layer provides an entry point for applications to access the protocol stack and prepare information for transmission across a network",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9781119807308/c06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0916",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You have just finished installing a web server farm on your company's network, along with a router to create a screened subnet (perimeter network) on which the web servers are located. However, you now cannot access the web servers from your workstation on the internal network. Which of the following is not one of the tasks you will have to complete before you can access the screened subnet from the internal network?",
        "choices": [
            "Change MAC addresses",
            "Change IP addresses",
            "Update the DNS records",
            "Change default gateway addresses"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Media Access Control (MAC) addresses are hard-coded into network interface adapters and are not easily changeable. There is also no need to change them for this purpose. First, you will have to change IP addresses of the web servers. This is because the computers on the other side of the router, on the screened subnet, must use an IP network address that is different from the internal network's address. Next, you will have to change the default gateway address setting on the internal network computers to the address of the router on the internal network so that traffic can be forwarded to the screened subnet. Finally, you will have to update the resource records on your Domain Name System (DNS) server to reflect the IP address changes",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9781119807308/c07.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-A0924",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following Power over Ethernet (PoE) specifications supplies power to devices using the spare wire pair on a 10Base-T or 100Base-TX twisted-pair network?",
        "choices": [
            "4PPoE",
            "Alternative A",
            "Alternative B",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "The Alternative B PoE variant can use the spare wire pair in a CAT 5 or better 10Base-T or 100Base-TX cable to supply power to connected devices. The Alternative A and 4PPoE variants cannot use the spare wire pair in this manner; they supply power using the wire pairs that carry data at the same time. For Gigabit Ethernet or faster installations, Alternative B is also capable of using the data wire pairs",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9781119807308/c07.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0053",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following Storage Area Network (SAN) protocols are capable of sharing a network medium with standard Local Area Network (LAN) traffic? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "iSCSI",
            "Fibre Channel",
            "FCoE",
            "InfiniBand"
        ],
        "answer": "A,C",
        "solution": "iSCSI runs on a standard IP network, and Fibre Channel over Ethernet (FCoE) runs on a standard Ethernet network. Both of these protocols can share a network with LAN traffic, although the use of a Quality of Service (QoS) mechanism is usually recommended. Fibre Channel and InfiniBand both require a dedicated network medium that does not support LAN traffic",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Fundamentals"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0063",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following physical network devices can conceivably be implemented as software in a computer's operating system? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "Hub",
            "Switch",
            "Router",
            "Firewall"
        ],
        "answer": "C,D",
        "solution": "Most operating systems are capable of functioning as routers or firewalls. To route traffic, the system must have two network connections. A software firewall can be part of a computer's routing functionality, or it can be a stand-alone firewall that protects only the local system. Computers cannot function as hubs or switches, because multiple ports would be required, and standard network adapters do not implement those functions",
        "topic": [
            "Network Implementations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0124",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "You are starting a new job, and the company's Human Resources (HR) department has asked you to sign an Acceptable Use Policy (AUP) regarding computer and network use. The document includes a privacy clause. Which of the following are specifications you can expect to find in this clause? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "Any emails you send or receive can be monitored by the company at any time.",
            "All files and data that you store on company computers must be accessible to the company for scanning and monitoring.",
            "All work that you perform for the company becomes the sole property of the company, including copyrights and patents.",
            "All hardware, software, and any proprietary data stored on the company's computers remains the property of the company."
        ],
        "answer": "A,B",
        "solution": "Clauses regarding company property, including the copyrights and patents for the work performed for the company, typically do appear in an AUP but not in the privacy clause. This information would be more likely to appear in an ownership clause. The privacy clause commonly explains that the company has the right to access and monitor anything stored on its computers",
        "topic": [
            "Network Operations"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0141",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following are terms for an area of an enterprise network, separated by firewalls, which contains servers that must be accessible both from the Internet and from the internal network? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "Intranet",
            "DMZ",
            "EGP",
            "Stateless network",
            "Perimeter network",
            "Screened subnet"
        ],
        "answer": "B,E,F",
        "solution": "Servers that must be accessible both from the internal network and from the Internet are typically located in an area of the enterprise called a screened subnet, a perimeter network, or a demilitarized zone (DMZ). This area is separated from both the Internet and the internal network by firewalls, which prevents unauthorized Internet users from accessing the internal network. Intranet is another term for the internal network. Edge Gateway Protocol (EGP) is a type of routing protocol, and stateless is a type of firewall; neither apply to this definition",
        "topic": [
            "Network Security"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0181",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following statements about running a site-to-site Virtual Private Network (VPN) connection to join two distant Local Area Networks (LANs) together, rather than using a Wide Area Network (WAN) connection, are generally true? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "The VPN is cheaper.",
            "The VPN is slower.",
            "The VPN is less secure.",
            "The VPN is harder to maintain."
        ],
        "answer": "A,B",
        "solution": "Because the two endpoints of a VPN are connecting to local Internet Service Providers (ISPs), the ongoing connection costs are typically much less than a long-distance WAN connection. However, in most cases, a VPN is slower because it is affected by Internet bandwidth use and other factors. VPN connections are not inherently less secure than WANs, and they are not necessarily more difficult to maintain",
        "topic": [
            "Network Security"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0198",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "On Monday morning, Alice arrives at work to find multiple email and telephone messages from users who are unable to access the Accounting department's file server. Which of the following are the best questions to ask during the beginning stage of the troubleshooting process? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "What has changed since the users were last able to access the server?",
            "Are there any software updates that Alice should apply to the server?",
            "Has the server suffered a hard disk failure?",
            "Which users are reporting a problem, and where are they located?"
        ],
        "answer": "A,D",
        "solution": "The first stage of the troubleshooting process calls for Alice to identify the problem by gathering information. Learning about who is reporting the problem and what has changed since the server was last accessible can provide Alice with information that could help her determine whether the problem is located in the users' workstations, somewhere in the network, or in the server itself. The other options are intended to test a theory about a probable cause, a troubleshooting stage that comes later",
        "topic": [
            "Network Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0207",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Ed is trying to troubleshoot a problem that has caused a wired network connection to fail completely. Which of the following wired network problems will cause a complete failure of a network connection? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "Bottleneck",
            "Speed mismatch",
            "Duplex mismatch",
            "TX/RX reversal",
            "Bad switch port"
        ],
        "answer": "B,D,E",
        "solution": "A speed mismatch on a wired network only occurs when two devices are configured to use a specific transmission speed and those speeds are different. In that case, network communication stops. For network communication to occur on a twisted-pair network, transmit (TX) pins must be connected to receive (RX) pins. If the connections are reversed, no communication occurs. If the switch port to which a computer is connected is bad, there will be no network communication. Bottlenecks and duplex mismatches will slow down network communications, but they will not stop them completely",
        "topic": [
            "Network Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0225",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Trixie has recently moved to a new office in her company's building, down the hall from her old one. Since the move, she has only been able to access the wireless network with her laptop intermittently. She never had a problem in her previous location. Which of the following could possibly be the cause of her problem? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "Trixie's new office is farther from the Access Point (AP) than her old one.",
            "Her laptop is connecting to the wrong SSID.",
            "The AP is using an omnidirectional antenna.",
            "There are too many walls between Trixie's new office and the AP."
        ],
        "answer": "A,D",
        "solution": "Greater distance from the AP or interference from intervening walls can both cause a weakening of wireless signals, resulting in the intermittent connectivity that Trixie is experiencing. An incorrect Service Set Identifier (SSID) would prevent Trixie's laptop from ever connecting to the network. An omnidirectional antenna generates signals in every direction, which would not account for Trixie's problem",
        "topic": [
            "Network Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0230",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Several accounting consultants are working in Ed's office for the first time, and they are unable to connect to the 802.11n wireless network with their laptops. Which of the following tasks should Ed perform first to try to resolve the problem? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "Check the network adapters in the laptops for channel overlap",
            "Make sure that the consultants are attempting to connect to the correct SSID",
            "Examine the area where the consultants are working for possible sources of signal interference",
            "Make sure that the consultants' laptops are configured to use the correct wireless encryption protocol"
        ],
        "answer": "B,D",
        "solution": "Of the options provided, the ones most likely to be causing the problem are the use of an incorrect Service Set Identifier (SSID) or encryption protocol. Although signal interference could possibly be a cause, it is more likely that the new users have devices that are incorrectly configured for Ed's network. Channel overlap is a problem that Ed would check and resolve at the Access Point (AP), not the users' workstations",
        "topic": [
            "Network Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9781119807308/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0268",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "You receive a call at the IT help desk from a user who has recently moved to a new office in the company building, down the hall from her old one. Since the move, she has only been able to access the company's wireless network with her laptop intermittently. The network is based on 802.11n equipment, and it is using the 2.4 GHz frequency and the WPA2 security protocol. The user never had a problem in her previous office location. Which of the following could not possibly be the cause of her problem? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "The user's laptop is connecting to the wrong SSID.",
            "The user's laptop is configured to use the 5 GHz frequency.",
            "The user's new office is farther from the access point than her old one.",
            "There are more intervening walls between the user's new office and the access point.",
            "The user's laptop is configured with the wrong WPA2 passphrase."
        ],
        "answer": "C,D",
        "solution": "An incorrect frequency, Service Set Identifier (SSID), or WiFi Protected Access II (WPA2) passphrase would prevent the user's laptop from ever connecting to the network, so these cannot be the cause of the problem. Greater distance from the access point or interference from intervening walls can both cause a weakening of wireless signals, which can result in the intermittent connectivity that the user is experiencing",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9781119807308/c06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119807308-B0275",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Originally, Storage Area Networks (SANs) were dedicated solely to storage-based traffic. A Local Area Network (LAN) was also required for other types of traffic. Today, however, it is possible for SAN and LAN traffic to coexist on a single network medium. Which of the following SAN protocols are capable of sharing a network medium with standard LAN traffic? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "InfiniBand",
            "Fibre Channel",
            "iSCSI",
            "FCoE"
        ],
        "answer": "C,D",
        "solution": "The iSCSI protocol runs on a standard IP network, and the Fibre Channel over Ethernet (FCoE) variant runs on a standard Ethernet network. Both of these protocols can share a network with LAN traffic, although the use of a Quality of Service (QoS) mechanism is usually recommended. The original Fibre Channel implementation and InfiniBand both require a dedicated network medium that does not support LAN traffic",
        "topic": [],
        "source": "9781119807308/c07.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0004",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "In a physical star topology, what happens when a workstation loses its physical connection to another device?",
        "choices": [
            "The ring is broken, so no devices can communicate.",
            "Only that workstation loses its ability to communicate.",
            "That workstation and the device it's connected to lose communication with the rest of the network.",
            "No devices can communicate because there are now two unterminated network segments."
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "In a star topology, each workstation connects to a hub, switch, or similar central device but not to other workstations. The benefit is that when connectivity to the central device is lost, the rest of the network lives on",
        "topic": [
            "Introduction to Networks"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0041",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You need to crimp on a connector using an RJ-45 connector. Which pin-out configuration would you use to connect a host to a switch?",
        "choices": [
            "UTP",
            "Straight-through",
            "Crossover",
            "Rolled"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "You would use a straight-through cable to connect a host to a switch, and the typical pin-out is called T568A",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Connectors and Wiring Standards"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0043",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What type of cable transmits lights from end to end?",
        "choices": [
            "Coax",
            "Fiber-optic",
            "UTP",
            "Category 2"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Remember that fiber-optic cable transmits a digital signal using light impulses. Light is carried on either a glass or a plastic core",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Connectors and Wiring Standards"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0057",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "How many devices in a collision domain have to listen when a single host talks?",
        "choices": [
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "One",
            "All"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "When one device sends a packet out on a network segment, all other devices on the same physical network segment must wait and let it be transmitted",
        "topic": [
            "The Current Ethernet Specifications"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0064",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What device can you not use full-duplex communication with?",
        "choices": [
            "Host",
            "Hub",
            "Switch",
            "Router"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Full-duplex communication cannot be used with a hub because a hub is a half-duplex single communication device. A host, switch, and router have the ability to process traffic (frames), whereas a hub is a multiport repeater",
        "topic": [
            "The Current Ethernet Specifications"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0074",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a term used when making SOHO Internet connections?",
        "choices": [
            "Hub",
            "Router",
            "NIC",
            "Switch",
            "IDS/IPS"
        ],
        "answer": "E",
        "solution": "Intrusion detection and prevention systems are not a requirement for a SOHO Internet connection",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Devices"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0076",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which device is used to segment a network?",
        "choices": [
            "Hub",
            "Switch",
            "Repeater",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "When we say segment, we mean to create multiple collision or broadcast domains. Hubs don't segment a network; they just connect network segments together. Repeaters don't segment the network; they repeat a signal and allow the distance covered to be increased. So the only correct option is B, a switch",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Devices"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0080",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following devices can work at both layers 2 and 3 of the OSI model?",
        "choices": [
            "Hub",
            "Switch",
            "Multilayer switch",
            "Bridge"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "A switch is typically just a layer 2 device segmenting the network by using MAC addresses. However, some higher-end switches can provide layer 3 services",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Devices"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0084",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What role does the A record in a Domain Name Service (DNS) server have in your network?",
        "choices": [
            "Translates human name to IP address",
            "Translates IP address to human name",
            "Enables printing, copying, and faxing from one device",
            "Controls network packets to optimize performance"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "DNS translates human names to IP addresses for routing your packet through the Internet. Hosts can receive the IP address of this DNS server and then resolve hostnames to IP addresses",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Devices"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0092",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which type of server in your network uses pointer and A records?",
        "choices": [
            "NAT translation server",
            "IDS/IPS server",
            "DNS server",
            "Proxy server"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "A DNS server uses many types of records. An A record is a hostname–to–IP address record, and a pointer record is an IP address–to–hostname record",
        "topic": [
            "Networking Devices"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0126",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You have a Class A host of 10.0.0.110/25. It needs to communicate to a host with an IP address of 10.0.0.210/25. Which of the following devices do you need to use in order for these hosts to communicate?",
        "choices": [
            "A layer 2 switch",
            "Router",
            "DNS server",
            "Hub"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Don't freak because this is a Class A. What is your subnet mask? 255.255.255.128. Regardless of the class of address, this is a block size of 128 in the fourth octet. The subnets are 0 and 128. The 0 subnet host range is 1–126, with a broadcast address of 127. The 128 subnet host range is 129–254, with a broadcast address of 255. You need a router for these two hosts to communicate because they are in different subnets",
        "topic": [
            "IP Subnetting, Troubleshooting IP, and Introduction to NAT"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c08.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0132",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "On which of the following devices are you most likely to be able to implement NAT?",
        "choices": [
            "Hub",
            "Ethernet switch",
            "Router",
            "Bridge"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Devices with layer 3 awareness, such as routers and firewalls, are the only ones that can manipulate the IP header in support of NAT",
        "topic": [
            "IP Subnetting, Troubleshooting IP, and Introduction to NAT"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c08.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0152",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Where does a frame have to carry a packet to if it is destined for a remote network?",
        "choices": [
            "Default gateway",
            "Neighbor host",
            "Switch",
            "Hub"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "I hope you said A! Packets specifically have to be carried to a router in order to be routed through a network",
        "topic": [
            "Introduction to IP Routing"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0176",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following features of a switch will allow two switches to pass VLAN network information?",
        "choices": [
            "PoE",
            "VLANs",
            "Trunking",
            "STP"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Trunking allows switches to pass information about many or all VLANs configured on the switches",
        "topic": [
            "Switching and Virtual LANs"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c11.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0267",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following provides the best way to shape a broadcast cell?",
        "choices": [
            "Antennas",
            "Power setting",
            "Repeaters",
            "Multiple APs"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "When you need to reshape the cell, you use antennas to accomplish this. For example, you may want to send the signal down a long hallway while not transmitting outside the hallway into the parking lot. That could be done with a directional antenna",
        "topic": [
            "Network Hardening Techniques"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c18.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0314",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What is the average of collected metrics called?",
        "choices": [
            "NetFlow",
            "SNMPv2c",
            "Management information base",
            "Baseline",
            "Syslog"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "A measurement is taken from network gear and servers to determine what is considered to be normal operations of a system",
        "topic": [
            "Ensuring Network Availability"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c22.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0339",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which tool would be used to connect wire between two punch-down block blades?",
        "choices": [
            "Punch-down tool",
            "Crimper",
            "Snips",
            "Strippers"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Just as it is named, a punch-down tool is used to “punch” a wire into a cable block. Crimpers are used to put a jack onto the end of a cable, and snips and strippers are used to prepare the cable",
        "topic": [
            "Cable Connectivity Issues and Tools"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c23.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0342",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which device monitors incoming voltage levels and overvoltage thresholds?",
        "choices": [
            "Repeater",
            "Toner probe",
            "VOM",
            "Surge protector"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "To measure AC power levels to make sure they are within specifications, a surge protector is used. They can also mitigate overvoltage conditions to protect the connected equipment",
        "topic": [
            "Cable Connectivity Issues and Tools"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c23.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-A0358",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "A user calls you, complaining that he can't access the corporate intranet web server. You try the same address, and you receive a Host Not Found error. Several minutes later, another user reports the same problem. You can still send email and transfer files to another server. What is the most likely cause of the problem?",
        "choices": [
            "The hub is unplugged.",
            "The server is not routing protocols to your workstation.",
            "The user's workstation is not connected to the network.",
            "The web server is down."
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "Because other people are experiencing the problem, most likely it is either network or server related. Because you can transfer files to and from another server, it can't be the network. Thus, the problem is related to the web server",
        "topic": [
            "Network Troubleshooting Methodology"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c24.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-B0002",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which layer 1 devices can be used to enlarge the area covered by a single LAN segment? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "Firewall",
            "NIC",
            "Hub",
            "Repeater",
            "RJ-45 transceiver"
        ],
        "answer": "C,D",
        "solution": "Not that you really want to enlarge a single collision domain, but a hub (multiport repeater) will provide this functionality for you",
        "topic": [
            "The Open Systems Interconnection Specifications"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9781119811633-B0019",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "What are the two categories of IGP protocols? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "Link state",
            "Static",
            "Distance vector",
            "EGP"
        ],
        "answer": "A,C",
        "solution": "Distance-vector (DV) and link-state (LS) are the two routing protocols to remember",
        "topic": [
            "Introduction to IP Routing"
        ],
        "source": "9781119811633/c09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136755562-A0012",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following fields in the HDLC header used by Cisco routers does Cisco add, beyond the ISO standard HDLC?",
        "choices": [
            "Flag",
            "Type",
            "Address",
            "FCS"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "The standard HDLC header does not include a Type field, which identifies the type of packet encapsulated inside the HDLC frame",
        "topic": [
            "Fundamentals of WANs and IP Routing"
        ],
        "source": "9780136755562/vol1_ch03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136755562-A0034",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Switch SW1 sends a frame to switch SW2 using 802.1Q trunking. Which of the answers describes how SW1 changes or adds to the Ethernet frame before forwarding the frame to SW2?",
        "choices": [
            "Inserts a 4-byte header and does change the MAC addresses",
            "Inserts a 4-byte header and does not change the MAC addresses",
            "Encapsulates the original frame behind an entirely new Ethernet header",
            "None of the other answers are correct"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "802.1Q defines a 4-byte header, inserted after the original frame’s destination and source MAC address fields. The insertion of this header does not change the original frame’s source or destination address. The header itself holds a 12-bit VLAN ID field, which identifies the VLAN associated with the frame",
        "topic": [
            "Implementing Ethernet Virtual LANs"
        ],
        "source": "9780136755562/vol1_ch08.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136755562-A0057",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following commands might you see associated with a router CLI, but not with a switch CLI?",
        "choices": [
            "The show mac address-table command",
            "The show ip route command",
            "The show running-config command",
            "The show interfaces status command"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Cisco routers that do not also have any Layer 2 switch features support commands needed for Layer 3 routing as well as commands in common between Layer 2 switching and Layer 3 routing devices. In this case, the **show interfaces status** and **show mac address-table** commands happen to be commands supported on Layer 2 switches but not on routers. Both types of devices use the **show running-config** command. Of the answers, only the **show ip interface brief** command is unique to routers",
        "topic": [
            "Operating Cisco Routers"
        ],
        "source": "9780136755562/vol1_ch15.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136755562-B0014",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "The output of the **show interfaces status** command on a 2960 switch shows interface Fa0/1 in a “disabled” state. Which of the following is true about interface Fa0/1? (Choose three answers.)",
        "choices": [
            "The interface is configured with the shutdown command.",
            "The show interfaces fa0/1 command will list the interface with two status codes of administratively down and line protocol down.",
            "The show interfaces fa0/1 command will list the interface with two status codes of up and down.",
            "The interface cannot currently be used to forward frames.",
            "The interface can currently be used to forward frames."
        ],
        "answer": "A,B,D",
        "solution": "The disabled state in the **show interfaces status** command is the same as an “administratively down and down” state shown in the **show interfaces** command. The interface must be in a connected state (per the **show interfaces status** command) before the switch can send frames out the interface",
        "topic": [
            "Configuring and Verifying Switch Interfaces"
        ],
        "source": "9780136755562/vol1_ch07.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136755562-B0060",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following parameters are necessary when creating a new WLAN with the controller GUI? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "SSID",
            "VLAN number",
            "Interface",
            "BSSID",
            "IP subnet"
        ],
        "answer": "A,C",
        "solution": "The SSID and controller interface are the only parameters from the list that are necessary. The VLAN number is not because it is supplied when a controller interface is configured",
        "topic": [
            "Building a Wireless LAN"
        ],
        "source": "9780136755562/vol1_ch29.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136755562-B0091",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Think about a policing function that is currently working, and also think about a shaping function that is also currently working. That is, the current bit rate of traffic exceeds the respective policing and shaping rates. Which statements are true about these features? (Choose two answers.)",
        "choices": [
            "The policer may or may not be discarding packets.",
            "The policer is definitely discarding packets.",
            "The shaper may or may not be queuing packets to slow down the sending rate.",
            "The shaper is definitely queuing packets to slow down the sending rate."
        ],
        "answer": "A,D",
        "solution": "Policers monitor the bit rate and take action if the bit rate exceeds the policing rate. However, the action can be to discard some packets, or to re-mark some packets, or even to do nothing to the packets, simply measuring the rate for later reporting. For shaping, when a shaper is enabled because the traffic has exceeded the shaping rate, the shaper always queues packets and slows the traffic. There is no option to re-mark the packets or to bypass the shaping function",
        "topic": [
            "Quality of Service (QoS)"
        ],
        "source": "9780136755562/vol2_ch11.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134307183-A0167",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which one of the following is a CCX Lite module?",
        "choices": [
            "CCXv1",
            "Voice",
            "Crypto",
            "Video"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "CCX Lite includes the Foundation, Voice, Location, and Management modules",
        "topic": [
            "Configuring Client Connectivity"
        ],
        "source": "9780134307183/ch17.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134307183-A0181",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "The IEEE 802.16 standard defines which one of the following technologies?",
        "choices": [
            "Token Ring",
            "ZigBee",
            "Bluetooth",
            "WiMAX"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "The IEEE 802.16 standard defines WiMAX",
        "topic": [
            "Dealing with Wireless Interference"
        ],
        "source": "9780134307183/ch19.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134307183-A0189",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "To get PI or a wireless controller to display information about a specific wireless client, you go to the **Monitor > Clients** page. Which one of the following pieces of information should you input to obtain the best troubleshooting data?",
        "choices": [
            "WLC IP address",
            "SSID",
            "Client’s MAC address",
            "AP name"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "By entering the client’s MAC address, the controller can display information about it straightaway. The other answers might also lead to useful information, but only after you spend more time sifting through the data",
        "topic": [
            "Troubleshooting WLAN Connectivity"
        ],
        "source": "9780134307183/ch20.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134307183-A0197",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Suppose you would like to scan the channels in the 5-GHz band to see which SSIDs are available to clients on which channels in a certain area. Which one of the following tools is a Wi-Fi scanner that is suited for this purpose?",
        "choices": [
            "Ekahau Site Survey Pro",
            "Savvius OmniPeek",
            "MetaGeek inSSIDer Office",
            "AirMagnet Spectrum XT"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "MetaGeek inSSIDer Office is a Wi-Fi scanner tool that can map service set identifiers (SSIDs) to channels for quick analysis. Other tools such as OmniPeek can achieve the same result, but they are packet analyzers and not strictly Wi-Fi scanners",
        "topic": [
            "Troubleshooting WLAN Connectivity"
        ],
        "source": "9780134307183/ch20.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134307183-B0018",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "If the IP address of an autonomous AP is not yet known, which of the following methods could you use to find it? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "DHCP server logs",
            "CDP",
            "AP console CLI",
            "AP management GUI"
        ],
        "answer": "A,B,C",
        "solution": "You can use all of the methods except the AP management GUI to find the AP’s IP address. Without the IP address, you would not be able to open a browser to the management GUI",
        "topic": [
            "Implementing Autonomous and Cloud Deployments"
        ],
        "source": "9780134307183/ch09.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134307183-B0029",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following parameters are necessary when creating a new WLAN with the controller GUI? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "SSID",
            "VLAN number",
            "Interface",
            "BSSID",
            "IP subnet"
        ],
        "answer": "A,C",
        "solution": "The SSID and controller interface are the only parameters from the list that are necessary. The VLAN number is not necessary because it is supplied when a controller interface is configured",
        "topic": [
            "Configuring a WLAN"
        ],
        "source": "9780134307183/ch15.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136555735-A0007",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "In Ethernet LANs, what is the functional equivalent to IGMPv3 in IPv6?",
        "choices": [
            "IGMPv3 includes IPv6 multicast support; that’s why it is v3.",
            "MLDv2.",
            "MLDv1.",
            "IPv6’s native support for multicast routing deprecates this need."
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "MLDv1 is similar to IGMPv2, and MLDv2 is similar to IGMPv3",
        "topic": [
            "Implementing Routing in the Data Center"
        ],
        "source": "9780136555735/ch01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136555735-B0008",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which Fabric Extender (FEX) topologies trade deterministic bandwidth for server-link stability during FEX uplink failure? (Choose two answers.)",
        "choices": [
            "Port channel",
            "Static pinning",
            "Virtual port channel",
            "Dynamic pinning",
            "Equal-cost multipath",
            "RPVST"
        ],
        "answer": "A,C",
        "solution": "Fabric Extender (FEX) supports the port channel and virtual port channel for uplink aggregation",
        "topic": [
            "Implementing Data Center Switching Protocols"
        ],
        "source": "9780136555735/ch02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138216993-A0073",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "The OSPFv3 hello packet uses the ___________ for the destination address.",
        "choices": [
            "MAC address 00:C1:00:5C:00:FF",
            "MAC address E0:00:00:06:00:AA",
            "IP address 224.0.0.8",
            "IP address 224.0.0.10",
            "IPv6 address FF02::A",
            "IPv6 address FF02::5"
        ],
        "answer": "F",
        "solution": "OSPFv3 uses link-local addresses for a majority of communication, but it uses the destination IPv6 address (FF02::5) for hello packets and link-state updates",
        "topic": [
            "OSPFv3"
        ],
        "source": "9780138216993/ch10.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138216993-A0111",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which traffic conditioning tool can be used to drop or mark down traffic that goes beyond a desired traffic rate?",
        "choices": [
            "Policers",
            "Shapers",
            "WRR",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Policers drop or re-mark incoming or outgoing traffic that goes beyond a desired traffic rate",
        "topic": [
            "Quality of Service (QoS)"
        ],
        "source": "9780138216993/ch14.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138216993-A0117",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which command displays the translation table on a router?",
        "choices": [
            "show ip translations",
            "show ip xlate",
            "show xlate",
            "show ip nat translations"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "The command **show ip nat translations** displays the active translation table on a NAT device",
        "topic": [
            "IP Services"
        ],
        "source": "9780138216993/ch15.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138216993-A0119",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "The IP translation table times out and clears dynamic TCP connection entries from the translation table after how long?",
        "choices": [
            "1 hour",
            "4 hours",
            "12 hours",
            "24 hours"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "The default NAT timeout is 24 hours",
        "topic": [
            "IP Services"
        ],
        "source": "9780138216993/ch15.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138216993-A0176",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which is the control plane used by SD-Access?",
        "choices": [
            "LISP control plane",
            "EPVN MP-BGP",
            "Multicast",
            "VXLAN control plane"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "The SD-Access fabric control plane is based on Locator/ID Separation Protocol (LISP)",
        "topic": [
            "Fabric Technologies"
        ],
        "source": "9780138216993/ch23.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138216993-A0209",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following is an architectural framework created by ETSI that defines standards to decouple network functions from proprietary hardware-based appliances and have them run in software on standard x86 servers?",
        "choices": [
            "VNF",
            "NFV",
            "NFVI",
            "NFVIS"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Network functions virtualization (NFV) is an architectural framework created by the European Telecommunications Standards Institute (ETSI) that defines standards to decouple network functions from proprietary hardware-based appliances and have them run in software on standard x86 servers. It also defines how to manage and orchestrate the network functions",
        "topic": [
            "Virtualization"
        ],
        "source": "9780138216993/ch27.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138216993-B0015",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following multicast address ranges match the administratively scoped block? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "239.0.0.0 to 239.255.255.255",
            "232.0.0.0 to 232.255.255.255",
            "224.0.0.0 to 224.0.0.255",
            "239.0.0.0/8",
            "224.0.1.0/24"
        ],
        "answer": "A,D",
        "solution": "239.0.0.0/8 (239.0.0.0 to 239.255.255.255) is the IANA IP multicast address range assigned to the administratively scoped block",
        "topic": [
            "Multicast"
        ],
        "source": "9780138216993/ch13.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138216993-B0028",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "LISP separates IP addresses into which of the following? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "RLOCs",
            "LISP entities",
            "Subnets and hosts",
            "EIDs"
        ],
        "answer": "A,D",
        "solution": "LISP separates IP addresses into endpoint identifiers (EIDs) and routing locators (RLOCs)",
        "topic": [
            "Overlay Tunnels"
        ],
        "source": "9780138216993/ch16.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136575474-A0052",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which CUBE manipulation technique can be leveraged to modify a SIP header in an egress 200 OK response to an INVITE?",
        "choices": [
            "Inbound SIP profile",
            "Outbound SIP profile",
            "Voice translation profile",
            "Voice translation rules"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Outbound SIP profiles are used to change egress SIP messaging on a given call leg",
        "topic": [
            "CUBE Call Routing and Digit Manipulation"
        ],
        "source": "9780136575474/ch08.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136575474-A0054",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which SIP header field is referenced by CUBE attempting to interwork a SIP REFER when configured for REFER consumption?",
        "choices": [
            "Referred-by",
            "To",
            "Request-uri",
            "Refer-to"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "The Refer-To header is used for dial peer lookups when CUBE has been configured to consume REFER requests",
        "topic": [
            "CUBE Interworking Features"
        ],
        "source": "9780136575474/ch09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136575474-B0019",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which troubleshooting tools allow you to view a ladder diagram of SIP signaling? (Choose three.)",
        "choices": [
            "Dialed Number Analyzer",
            "SIP Call Processor",
            "TranslatorX",
            "Real-Time Monitoring Tool",
            "Collaboration Solutions Analyzer"
        ],
        "answer": "C,D,E",
        "solution": "TranslatorX, RTMT, and CSA all have the ability to display a SIP ladder diagram for calls",
        "topic": [
            "Unified CM Call Routing and Digit Manipulation"
        ],
        "source": "9780136575474/ch04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136575474-B0038",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "What types of manipulations can be performed by a voice translation profile? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "SIP alphanumeric user ID",
            "Numeric called number",
            "Numeric calling number",
            "SIP alphanumeric host"
        ],
        "answer": "B,C",
        "solution": "The numeric calling number and numerical called number can be modified with translation profiles",
        "topic": [
            "CUBE Call Routing and Digit Manipulation"
        ],
        "source": "9780136575474/ch08.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136733867-A0005",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following options on a Cisco Expressway is used as a call forwarding feature for users?",
        "choices": [
            "RMS",
            "FindMe",
            "MRA",
            "Interworking",
            "Single Number Reach",
            "Extension Mobility"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "FindMe, also called User Policy, is by design an advanced call forwarding mechanism. It allows calls to a specified alias to be transferred automatically if the call is busy or there is no answer within a specified time frame. Rich Media Services (RMS) licenses are used on an Expressway for special calling scenarios. Mobile and Remote Access (MRA) is a proxy registration solution. Single Number Reach is a call forwarding solution on the CUCM Express, and Extension Mobility is a call forwarding solution on the Unified CM. Neither of these is supported on the Cisco Expressway",
        "topic": [
            "Introduction to the Cisco Expressway Solution"
        ],
        "source": "9780136733867/ch01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136733867-A0008",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "How many simultaneous video calls are supported through the Cisco Expressway with a Medium VM deployment?",
        "choices": [
            "100",
            "200",
            "250",
            "500"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "The CE1200 Appliance server and a large VM can both support up to 500 video calls and 1000 audio-only calls. The medium-density VM can support 100 video calls or 200 audio-only calls, and the small VM can support 40 MRA video or 20 non-MRA video calls and 40 audio-only calls",
        "topic": [
            "Introduction to the Cisco Expressway Solution"
        ],
        "source": "9780136733867/ch01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136733867-A0015",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Calls that utilize the interworking functionality are considered what type of call?",
        "choices": [
            "Registered",
            "Rich Media Session",
            "B2B",
            "Audio-only"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Calls for which the Expressway acts as a SIP to H.323 gateway are Rich Media Session (RMS) calls",
        "topic": [
            "Initial Configuration Settings on the Cisco Expressway"
        ],
        "source": "9780136733867/ch03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136733867-A0038",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Under which of the following Cisco Expressway menus can an administrator access the Locate tool?",
        "choices": [
            "Status",
            "System",
            "Configuration",
            "Applications",
            "Users",
            "Maintenance"
        ],
        "answer": "F",
        "solution": "To access the Locate tool, from the web interface of the Expressway, navigate to **Maintenance** > **Tools** > **Locate",
        "topic": [
            "Cisco Expressway Call Processing Order"
        ],
        "source": "9780136733867/ch07.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136733867-B0005",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "When registering an endpoint to the Cisco Expressway, what functions are the devices registering to? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "SIP registrar",
            "SIP AOR",
            "323 gateway",
            "323 gatekeeper",
            "320 gatekeeper"
        ],
        "answer": "A,D",
        "solution": "The Expressway can act as an H.323 gatekeeper and/or SIP registrar",
        "topic": [
            "Initial Configuration Settings on the Cisco Expressway"
        ],
        "source": "9780136733867/ch03.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136602804-A0032",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which tenant does ACI use to push configurations to switches in-band?",
        "choices": [
            "Mgmt",
            "User",
            "Infra",
            "Common"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Fabric APICs push policy to leaf switches via in-band connections into the infra tenant. The infra tenant forms both the underlay and overlay for intra-fabric communication. The infra tenant does not get exposed to the user space (tenants), and it has its own private network space and bridge domains",
        "topic": [
            "Tenant Building Blocks"
        ],
        "source": "9780136602804/ch05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136602804-A0033",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which tenant allows deployment of a shared L3Out?",
        "choices": [
            "Mgmt",
            "User",
            "Infra",
            "Common"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "The common tenant is a special tenant whose purpose is to provide common services to other tenants in an ACI fabric. The common tenant enables the creation of shared L3Outs, shared bridge domains, and shared VRF instances",
        "topic": [
            "Tenant Building Blocks"
        ],
        "source": "9780136602804/ch05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136602804-A0037",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following defines the action that should be taken on interesting traffic?",
        "choices": [
            "Filter",
            "Filter entry",
            "Subject",
            "Contract"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "A filter matches interesting traffic and consists of a series of filter entries. A subject determines the action to be taken on traffic that is matched, and a contract is directionally applied to EPGs to determine the traffic flows to which the contract applies",
        "topic": [
            "Tenant Building Blocks"
        ],
        "source": "9780136602804/ch05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136602804-A0045",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Before a tenant administrator maps an EPG to ports and encapsulations, he or she should first bind the EPG to one or more _________.",
        "choices": [
            "endpoints",
            "VRF instances",
            "AAEPs",
            "domains"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "A tenant administrator who wants to map an EPG to ports and encapsulations should first bind the EPG to a domain. The domain association by the tenant administrator acts as authorization that the endpoints within the specified EPG are indeed meant to connect to the fabric via the method specified by the domain. The domains that are bound to the EPG also indicate which VLAN IDs are acceptable encapsulations for the EPG",
        "topic": [
            "Access Policies"
        ],
        "source": "9780136602804/ch06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136602804-A0051",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following need to be directly associated with node IDs?",
        "choices": [
            "Interface profiles",
            "AAEPs",
            "Switch profiles",
            "Interface policies"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "A switch profile is a logical object that represents one or more physical switches from a configuration standpoint and directly points to node IDs. The use of switch profiles provides part of the basis for stateless networking in ACI",
        "topic": [
            "Access Policies"
        ],
        "source": "9780136602804/ch06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136602804-A0071",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "An ACI administrator wants to deploy an L3Out to ASR 1000 Series routers in a user VRF while ensuring that future L3Outs in other tenants can also reuse the same physical connectivity to the outside routers. Which interface type should be used?",
        "choices": [
            "Routed subinterfaces",
            "Routed interfaces",
            "SVIs",
            "Floating SVIs"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "When connecting ACI to a router (as opposed to a Layer 3 switch), there is very little to no benefit gained when using SVIs. There is also no use case for floating SVIs in this situation because there is minimal potential for workload movement when connecting to physical routers. Use of routed interfaces rules out deployment of further L3Outs from other VRFs on the same interface(s). Routed subinterfaces, on the other hand, enable reuse of physical interfaces for Layer 3 extension of regular user VRFs. Each encapsulation can be tied to a different L3Out",
        "topic": [
            "L3Outs"
        ],
        "source": "9780136602804/ch09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136602804-A0073",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which interface type is ideal for L3Out deployment when a physical firewall appliance needs to be dual-homed to a pair of leaf switches and establish routing protocol adjacencies directly with an ACI fabric?",
        "choices": [
            "Routed subinterfaces",
            "Routed interfaces",
            "SVIs",
            "Floating SVIs"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "In this case, a vPC can be configured for connectivity to the firewall, and an L3Out can be deployed using SVIs to enable peering with the firewall. Floating SVIs is not the best choice because the question specifies that the firewall is a physical appliance, and therefore there is no expectation for firewall connections to move between switches",
        "topic": [
            "L3Outs"
        ],
        "source": "9780136602804/ch09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136602804-B0008",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following tools can be used to query the ACI object hierarchy? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "MOQuery",
            "Find",
            "Grep",
            "Visore"
        ],
        "answer": "A,D",
        "solution": "MOQuery is a CLI-based tool used for querying the ACI object hierarchy, and Visore is the GUI-based equivalent",
        "topic": [
            "Exploring ACI"
        ],
        "source": "9780136602804/ch04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138217464-A0034",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "You have a DMVPN network that has a hub and three spokes. The spokes are not learning the routes of the other spokes. Of the following options, which is most likely the reason for this?",
        "choices": [
            "Split horizon is enabled on the GRE interfaces of the spokes.",
            "Split horizon is enabled on the hub’s mGRE interface.",
            "Split horizon is disabled on the hub’s mGRE interface.",
            "Split horizon is disabled on the GRE interfaces of the spokes."
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "When Split horizon is enabled on the hub’s mGRE interface the spokes will not learn the routes of the other spokes",
        "topic": [
            "Troubleshooting EIGRP for IPv4"
        ],
        "source": "9780138217464/ch04.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138217464-A0036",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What address does the EIGRPv6 hello packet use for the destination address?",
        "choices": [
            "MAC address 00:C1:00:5C:00:FF",
            "MAC address E0:00:00:06:00:AA",
            "IP address 224.0.0.8",
            "IP address 224.0.0.10",
            "IPv6 address FF02::A",
            "IPv6 address FF02::8"
        ],
        "answer": "E",
        "solution": "EIGRPv6 uses link-local addresses for a majority of communication, but it uses the destination IPv6 address FF02::A for hello, query, and update packets",
        "topic": [
            "EIGRPv6"
        ],
        "source": "9780138217464/ch05.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138217464-A0109",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "R1 learns the 10.11.11.0/24 prefix from EIGRP. EIGRP is redistributed into OSPF on R1, and OSPF is redistributed into BGP on R1. R1 advertises all the BGP network prefixes to R3. Does R3 receive the 10.11.11.0/24 prefix?",
        "choices": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Route redistribution is not transitive on a single router",
        "topic": [
            "Route Redistribution"
        ],
        "source": "9780138217464/ch16.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138217464-A0112",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "R1 learns the 10.11.11.0/24 prefix from EIGRP. EIGRP is redistributed into OSPF on R1. R1 has an OSPF adjacency with R2. R2 redistributes OSPF into BGP. R2 advertises all BGP network prefixes to R3. Does R3 receive the 10.11.11.0/24 prefix?",
        "choices": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Sequential redistribution is allowed",
        "topic": [
            "Route Redistribution"
        ],
        "source": "9780138217464/ch16.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138217464-B0020",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "OSPF neighborships have been successfully formed throughout the entire routing domain. Which of the following are reasons any router may be missing routes in the local LSDB or the local routing table? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "The missing route’s network interface has been configured as passive.",
            "There are duplicate router IDs in the routing domain.",
            "There is an outbound distribute list configured.",
            "The spoke is the DR in a hub-and-spoke topology."
        ],
        "answer": "B,D",
        "solution": "Duplicate router IDs in the routing domain and a spoke being the DR in a hub and spoke topology are reasons why any router may be missing routes in the local LSDB or the local routing table",
        "topic": [
            "Troubleshooting OSPFv2"
        ],
        "source": "9780138217464/ch08.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780138217464-B0030",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "What could prevent a route from being advertised to another BGP router? (Choose three.)",
        "choices": [
            "Mismatched timers",
            "Split-horizon rule",
            "Missing network mask command",
            "Route filtering"
        ],
        "answer": "B,C,D",
        "solution": "The split-horizon rule, a missing **network mask** command or route filtering could prevent a route from being advertised to another BGP router",
        "topic": [
            "Troubleshooting BGP"
        ],
        "source": "9780138217464/ch14.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136575160-A0020",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which protocol maps names to IPv6 addresses?",
        "choices": [
            "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)",
            "Neighbor Discovery (ND)",
            "Domain Name System (DNS)",
            "DNSv2"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "The DNS maps fully qualified domain names to IPv6 addresses using (AAAA) records",
        "topic": [
            "Internet Protocol Version 6 (IPv6) Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780136575160/ch02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136575160-A0046",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which SNMP component contains an agent?",
        "choices": [
            "Managed device",
            "Agent",
            "NMS manager",
            "MIB"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Managed devices contain SNMP agents",
        "topic": [
            "IP Multicast and Network Management"
        ],
        "source": "9780136575160/ch05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136575160-A0056",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which type of cable is the best solution in terms of cost for connecting an access switch to the distribution layer requiring 140 meters?",
        "choices": [
            "UTP",
            "Copper",
            "Multimode fiber",
            "Single-mode fiber"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Multimode fiber provide a cost-effective solution for that distance. Single-mode fiber is more expensive. UTP’s maximum distance is 100 meters",
        "topic": [
            "Enterprise LAN Design and Technologies"
        ],
        "source": "9780136575160/ch06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136575160-A0059",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which solution remotely powers up a machine?",
        "choices": [
            "PoE",
            "WoL",
            "OOB switch",
            "ON switch"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Wake on LAN (WoL) is a combination of hardware and software technologies to wake up sleeping systems. The WoL feature allows an administrator to remotely power up all sleeping machines so that they can receive updates",
        "topic": [
            "Enterprise LAN Design and Technologies"
        ],
        "source": "9780136575160/ch06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136600992-A0003",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Suppose you collect information about the wireless devices that will be used at a customer’s site. Which one of the following specifications will determine which bands you should enable in your wireless design?",
        "choices": [
            "802.11b/g/n",
            "Data rates: 6–54Mbps",
            "Antenna gain: 2.0 dBi",
            "Sensitivity: −90 dBm"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "The specification of 802.11b/g/n reveals that the device will operate only on the 2.4 GHz band. Even though “n” supports 2.4 and 5GHz bands, its combination with “b” and “g” commonly refers to only the 2.4GHz band. Support for the 5 GHz band would be implied with the inclusion of “a,” “ac,” or “ax”, as in “802.11a/b/g/n/ac”",
        "topic": [
            "Wireless Design Requirements"
        ],
        "source": "9780136600992/ch01.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136600992-A0011",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "A wireless associate claims to have measured a 25 dB attenuation behind a concrete wall and asserts that the common reference table indicates 12 dB is wrong. What can you tell the associate?",
        "choices": [
            "The associate may have measured the attenuation from the middle of the room instead of right behind the wall, thus leading to the discrepancy.",
            "The table is only indicative. Local differences may be found, and this is why surveys are important.",
            "The table is old. Newer walls have metal reinforcement that increases the attenuation.",
            "The table indicates the one-way attenuation, but Wi-Fi communication is bidirectional, so 24 to 25 dB is correct."
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Attenuation tables are only intended to reflect common values; they are not absolute references. Attenuation would be worse close to the wall (because it would measure near field attenuation instead of far field). Attenuation reflects the signal loss between a transmitter and a receiver; the fact that communication could be unidirectional or bidirectional is irrelevant",
        "topic": [
            "Conducting an Offsite Site Survey"
        ],
        "source": "9780136600992/ch02.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136600992-A0077",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which EDCA metric defines how long a station may continue transmitting?",
        "choices": [
            "AIFSN",
            "CWmin",
            "CWmax",
            "TXOP",
            "TSpec"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "The TXOP (Transmission Opportunity) is the metric defined that allows a station to continually transmit until the timer expires. The TXOP interval is unique per AC",
        "topic": [
            "Implementing Quality of Service on a Wireless Network"
        ],
        "source": "9780136600992/ch11.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136600992-A0084",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which one of the following allows a WLC to determine if an AP has any active multicast recipients for a specific group address?",
        "choices": [
            "Entries in its ARP table",
            "IGMP snooping",
            "A valid CAPWAP group address",
            "IGMP membership reports sent from the router"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Through IGMP snooping, the controller can eavesdrop and learn about multicast groups that wireless clients have joined. The WLC will also know which APs those clients are associated with",
        "topic": [
            "Implementing Multicast"
        ],
        "source": "9780136600992/ch12.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136600992-A0086",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "In order to assist Apple devices to discover online resources with the Bonjour protocol, which one of the following features should be configured?",
        "choices": [
            "IGMP snooping",
            "Bonjour Direct",
            "mDNS snooping",
            "Multicast Direct"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "The Bonjour protocol uses mDNS to discover resources that are available on a network. However, the discovery requests and advertisements must stay within the same IP subnet. You should configure mDNS snooping to enable a controller to intercept Bonjour messages and relay them across subnets and VLANs when necessary",
        "topic": [
            "Implementing Multicast"
        ],
        "source": "9780136600992/ch12.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136600992-A0110",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "In what state will your WLC CLI report a client with a static IP address that just completed L2 authentication?",
        "choices": [
            "Run",
            "Authcheck complete",
            "DHCP_fail",
            "DHCP_reqd"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "By default, a client that completes L2 authentication moves to the DHCP_reqd state. It is only after the WLC detects that the client uses a static IP address (seeing client data traffic) that the WLC understands that no DHCP phase is required, and the client is moved to Run state. Authcheck appears during the L2 authentication phase, and the end of the L2 authentication phase is labeled L2authcomplete. DHCP_fail is not a valid message",
        "topic": [
            "Monitoring and Troubleshooting WLAN Components"
        ],
        "source": "9780136600992/ch16.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136589716-A0107",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "After you deploy a new NAT policy, if a connection still uses a rule from the prior version of the NAT policy, how could you ensure that the threat defense will use the new policy?",
        "choices": [
            "Deploy the NAT policy one more time.",
            "Make the NAT rule more specific.",
            "Clear the current translation table.",
            "All of these answers are correct."
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Clearing the current translation table ensures that the threat defense will use the new policy",
        "topic": [
            "Network Address Translation (NAT)"
        ],
        "source": "9780136589716/ch17.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136677710-A0025",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following are non-802.1X authentications?",
        "choices": [
            "WebAuth, MAB, EasyConnect, remote-access VPNs",
            "Remote access, WebAuth, EAP-MSChapV2",
            "PAP, LWA, RA VPN",
            "WebAuth, EAP-GTC, HTTP POST"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "**Explanation:** The four main non-802.1X authentication use cases are WebAuth (CWA and LWA), MAB, EasyConnect, and remote-access VPNs",
        "topic": [
            "1X Authentication"
        ],
        "source": "9780136677710/ch04.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136677710-A0030",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following are three possible options for Change of Authorization actions?",
        "choices": [
            "IKEv1, IKEv2, SSL",
            "HTTP, FTP, Telnet",
            "No COA, port bounce, reauthenticate",
            "User mode, privileged mode, configuration mode"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "**Explanation:** In a situation where a CoA is warranted, an authentication server can perform a number of actions, including no COA (that is, do nothing), port bounce (that is, whether to shut the relevant access port), or reauthenticate (that is, force the endpoint to reauthenticate in cases where multiple endpoints are present on a single access medium). Supported CoA actions may vary depending on the authentication server",
        "topic": [
            "Introduction to Advanced Concepts"
        ],
        "source": "9780136677710/ch05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136677710-A0085",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which host mode permits a virtually unlimited number of endpoints per port, allowing all subsequent MAC addresses to share the authorization result of the first endpoint authorized?",
        "choices": [
            "Single-Host",
            "MDA",
            "Multi-Auth",
            "Multi-Hosts"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "**Explanation:** Multi-Hosts mode is not commonly used, but it is a valid option. Much like Multi-Auth mode, Multi-Hosts mode is an extension to MDA. There is one authentication on the voice domain, and there is one authentication on the data domain. All other hosts on the data domain are allowed onto the network using the first successful authentication. It’s an “authenticate one, allow the rest” model",
        "topic": [
            "Implement Wired and Wireless Authentication"
        ],
        "source": "9780136677710/ch11.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136677710-B0032",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following are modes of SXP peers? (Choose two.)",
        "choices": [
            "Speaker",
            "SGT-Reflector",
            "Listener",
            "SGT-Sender"
        ],
        "answer": "A,C",
        "solution": "**Explanation:** Every SXP peer session has a speaker and a listener. A speaker sends the mappings of IP addresses to SGTs. The listener receives those updates and records them. A peer can be configured to be both a speaker and a listener for the same peer if both support it. It may have numerous peers as well",
        "topic": [
            "TrustSec and MACsec"
        ],
        "source": "9780136677710/ch17.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136634829-A0026",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What key word on a hub router enables connections from any remote spokes?",
        "choices": [
            "multicast",
            "dynamic",
            "host",
            "map"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "The **dynamic** keyword in the NHRP command **ip nhrp map multicast dynamic** enables spokes to attach",
        "topic": [
            "Dynamic Multipoint Virtual Private Network (DMVPN)"
        ],
        "source": "9780136634829/ch05.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136634829-A0034",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What command on the hub router enables you to determine whether the IKEv2 process has completed?",
        "choices": [
            "show crypto ikev2 authorization policy",
            "show crypto ikev2 profile",
            "show crypto ikev2 sa",
            "show ip interface brief"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "The **show crypto ikev2 sa** command shows whether the IKEv2 process has completed",
        "topic": [
            "FlexVPN Configuration and Troubleshooting"
        ],
        "source": "9780136634829/ch06.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-A0073",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following MPLS L3VPN RD allocation models provides active/active or active/standby connectivity to a multihomed remote site?",
        "choices": [
            "Unique RD per VPN per interface of each PE",
            "Unique RD per VPN",
            "Unique RD per VPN per PE"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Explanation: The unique RD per VPN per provider edge (PE) allocation model provides both active/active and active/standby connectivity design options for a multihomed remote site",
        "topic": [
            "Network Virtualization"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-A0079",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which MPLS L3VPN topology should be used if an enterprise is required to share the corporate internet service with all MPLS customer VPNs?",
        "choices": [
            "Full mesh",
            "Hub and spoke",
            "Multilevel hub and spoke",
            "Extranet and shared services"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "Explanation: The extranet and shared services MPLS L3VPN topology allows for resources to be properly shared between different VRFs and VPNs within the MPLS environment. In this case, the Internet service is the resource being shared. This is accomplished by setting the proper route target imports and exports",
        "topic": [
            "Network Virtualization"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-A0080",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the follow SDN mechanisms is defined by the physical switches and routers that are part of the local-area network?",
        "choices": [
            "Underlay",
            "SDN controller",
            "Overlay",
            "VN"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Explanation: The underlay network is defined specifically by the physical switches and routers in the LAN",
        "topic": [
            "Network Virtualization"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-A0081",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following is an SD-WAN overlay mechanism that provides segmentation much like a VRF?",
        "choices": [
            "Underlay",
            "SDN controller",
            "Overlay",
            "VN"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "Explanation: In the SD-WAN overlay, virtual networks (VNs) provide segmentation just like VRFs",
        "topic": [
            "Network Virtualization"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-A0102",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which multicast switching protocol should be used to limit the flooding of multicast IPv4 packets on a switch?",
        "choices": [
            "MLD snooping",
            "PIM",
            "IGMP snooping",
            "Auto-RP"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Explanation: Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP) snooping is a Layer 2 multicast protocol running on IPv4 networks that listens on multicast protocol packets between a Layer 3 multicast device and user hosts to maintain outbound interfaces of multicast packets. Multicasts may be filtered from the links that do not need them, conserving bandwidth on those links",
        "topic": [
            "Multicast Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch13.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-A0103",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which multicast switching protocol should be used to limit the flooding of multicast IPv6 packets on a switch?",
        "choices": [
            "MLD snooping",
            "PIM",
            "IGMP snooping",
            "Auto-RP"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Explanation: Multicast Listener Discovery (MLD) snooping is a Layer 2 multicast protocol running on IPv6 networks that listens on multicast protocol packets between a Layer 3 multicast device and user hosts to maintain outbound interfaces of multicast packets. MLD snooping manages and controls multicast packet forwarding at the data link layer. Think of MLD snooping as IGMP snooping but for IPv6",
        "topic": [
            "Multicast Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch13.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-A0111",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What is the first step an enterprise should take when migrating to an IPv6-only network if it wants to ensure that no service interruption occurs?",
        "choices": [
            "Leverage an overlay, like VXLAN, to support IPv6 hosts within the data center.",
            "Leverage a translation mechanism that is based on a load balancer, pure DNS, or classical NAT64.",
            "Migrate certain modules of the enterprise network first while leveraging a translation/tunneling mechanism to maintain communication between IPv6 and IPv4 islands.",
            "Migrate the core to be in dual-stack mode first, then migrate the other modules as time allows."
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "Explanation: Migrate the core to be in dual-stack mode first, and then other enterprise modules can be gradually migrated to IPv6-only or dual stack, depending on the goals and requirements of the business. Migrating to IPv6 this way ensures there is no service interruption",
        "topic": [
            "Network Services and Management"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch14.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-A0112",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following IPv6 design approaches for migrating to IPv6 would allow a network to provide IPv6 access inbound or outbound at the enterprise Internet edge?",
        "choices": [
            "Leveraging an overlay, like VXLAN, to support IPv6 hosts within the data center",
            "Leveraging a translation mechanism that is based on a load balancer, pure DNS, or classical NAT64",
            "Migrating certain modules of the enterprise network first while leveraging a translation/tunneling mechanism to maintain communication between IPv6 and IPv4 islands",
            "Migrating the core to be in dual-stack mode first, then migrating the other modules as time allows"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Explanation: To provide IPv6 access either inbound or outbound at the enterprise Internet edge, a translation mechanism is required that is either based on a load balancer, pure DNS, or classical NAT64",
        "topic": [
            "Network Services and Management"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch14.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-B0008",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which EIGRP packet types are sent using multicast? (Choose all that apply.)",
        "choices": [
            "Hello",
            "Reply",
            "Acknowledgement",
            "Update",
            "Query"
        ],
        "answer": "A,D,E",
        "solution": "Explanation: Neighborship is discovered and maintained using hello packets. These packets are sent using multicast. Update messages are used to send routing information to neighbors. These packets are sent to either one neighbor via unicast or to multiple neighbors via multicast. They are sent using Reliable Transport Protocol. EIGRP uses query packets when a router loses a path to a network. The router sends a query packet to its neighbors, asking if they have information on that network. These packets are sent via multicast and using Reliable Transport Protocol",
        "topic": [
            "Layer 3 Technologies"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch08.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-B0009",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which EIGRP packets use the Reliable Transport Protocol?",
        "choices": [
            "Hello",
            "Reply",
            "Acknowledgement",
            "Update",
            "Query"
        ],
        "answer": "B,D,E",
        "solution": "Explanation: Update messages are used to send routing information to neighbors. These packets are sent to either one neighbor via unicast or to multiple neighbors via multicast. They are sent using Reliable Transport Protocol. EIGRP uses query packets when a router loses a path to a network. The router sends a query packet to its neighbors, asking if they have information on that network. These packets are sent via multicast and using Reliable Transport Protocol. Reply packets are used by routers that received the query packet to respond to the query. These are sent unicast to the router that sent the query and are sent using Reliable Transport Protocol",
        "topic": [
            "Layer 3 Technologies"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch08.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137601066-B0016",
        "type": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following are factors that should be considered when selecting the placement of a multicast RP? (Choose three.)",
        "choices": [
            "Application multicast requirements",
            "Embedded-RP",
            "Multicast protocol",
            "Multicast tree",
            "RPF",
            "Phantom RP"
        ],
        "answer": "A,C,D",
        "solution": "Explanation: There are four factors that influence the placement of a multicast RP: the multicast protocol that is used, the multicast tree model, the application multicast requirements, and a targeted network segment between the sources and receivers (LAN versus WAN)",
        "topic": [
            "Multicast Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780137601066/ch13.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136677314-A0056",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What is the managed object browser called in Cisco UCS Manager?",
        "choices": [
            "Mobrowser",
            "UCSMobrowser",
            "Visore",
            "UCSVisore"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Cisco UCS Manager provides a managed object browser called Visore. Visore can be accessed by navigating to https://<UCS-Manager-IP>/visore.html",
        "topic": [
            "Cisco Data Center and Compute Management Platforms and APIs"
        ],
        "source": "9780136677314/ch09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136677314-A0102",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What Cisco NSO component manages the YANG data models that get sent to a device?",
        "choices": [
            "Service Manager",
            "Device Manager",
            "Core Engine",
            "CDB"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "The NSO Device Manager manages network devices using YANG data models and NETCONF. For devices that natively implement NETCONF and YANG models, the device manager is automatic, and devices that do not support NETCONF are integrated in the platform by using Network Element Drivers (NEDs)",
        "topic": [
            "Infrastructure Automation"
        ],
        "source": "9780136677314/ch15.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780137370337-A0071",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Intent-based networking transforms a hardware-centric network of manually provisioned devices into a controller-centric network that uses ____________ translated into policies that are automated and applied consistently across the network.",
        "choices": [
            "Business requirements",
            "Software definitions",
            "Routing protocols",
            "Artificial intelligence"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Intent-based networking is aligned to business requirements that are easily translated into policies reflecting native device configurations. All the other options are incorrect; the software image of a device does not make it intent-based; the routing protocols do not make a network intent-based, even if the routing protocols are defined similarly in an IBN; and AI does not intuit business requirements. It may inform you of what is more predominant or what is out of the norm",
        "topic": [
            "Infrastructure"
        ],
        "source": "9780137370337/ch09.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780136807964-A0102",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Chelin is an analyst in a security operations center (SOC) investigating an incident where large amounts of IP traffic (data) is leaving the organization late at night to suspicious hosts on the Internet. What technology could help Chelin obtain network metadata in an effective manner to detect such suspicious activity?",
        "choices": [
            "IPS",
            "NetFlow",
            "Full packet capture",
            "None of these answers are correct."
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "NetFlow can help security analysts obtain network traffic metadata in an effective manner to detect abnormal network activity",
        "topic": [
            "Network Infrastructure Device Telemetry and Analysis"
        ],
        "source": "9780136807964/ch10.xhtml"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0006",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which design solution states that a design must start from the application layer and finish in the physical layer?",
        "choices": [
            "OSI model",
            "[PPDIOO](gloss01.html#gloss_180)",
            "Hierarchical architecture",
            "Top-down"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "The top-down design approach starts the design from the application layer",
        "topic": [
            "Network Design Methodology"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch01.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0016",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What device filters broadcasts?",
        "choices": [
            "Layer 2 switch",
            "Hub",
            "Layer 3 switch",
            "Router",
            "a and c",
            "a and d",
            "a, c, and d"
        ],
        "answer": "F",
        "solution": "Routers and Layer 3 switches are Layer 3 devices that control and filter network broadcasts",
        "topic": [
            "Enterprise LAN Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch03.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0018",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What device limits the collision domain?",
        "choices": [
            "Layer 2 switch",
            "Hub",
            "Layer 3 switch",
            "Router",
            "a and c",
            "c and d",
            "a, c, and d"
        ],
        "answer": "G",
        "solution": "Every port of a Layer 2 switch, Layer 3 switch, or LAN port on a router is a collision domain",
        "topic": [
            "Enterprise LAN Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch03.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0020",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What type of LAN switches are preferred in the campus backbone of an enterprise network?",
        "choices": [
            "Layer 2 switches",
            "Layer 3 switches",
            "Layer 3 hubs",
            "Hubs"
        ],
        "answer": "B",
        "solution": "Layer 3 switches are recommended for the backbone of campus networks",
        "topic": [
            "Enterprise LAN Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch03.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0022",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which type of cable is the best solution in terms of cost for connecting an access switch to the distribution layer requiring 140 meters?",
        "choices": [
            "UTP",
            "Copper",
            "Multimode fiber",
            "Single-mode fiber"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Multimode fiber provides a cost-effective solution for that distance. Single-mode fiber is more expensive. UTP cannot go more than 100 meters",
        "topic": [
            "Enterprise LAN Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch03.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0031",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which network load balancing option maintains TCP state information locally in its state tables?",
        "choices": [
            "DNS based",
            "Anycast based",
            "Dedicated L4-7 load balancer",
            "ECMP"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "Dedicated L4-7 load balancers maintain TCP state information locally in their state tables",
        "topic": [
            "Data Center Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch04.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0044",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which of the following VPNs provides an alternative to MPLS WAN services?",
        "choices": [
            "GRE VPN",
            "Extranet VPN",
            "Remote access VPN",
            "[Site-to-site VPN](gloss01.html#gloss_125)"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "Site-to-site VPNs over the Internet offer an alternative WAN transport for interconnecting sites instead of MPLS",
        "topic": [
            "WAN Technologies and the Enterprise Edge"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch06.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0054",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What WAN/MAN architecture is provided by the service provider and has excellent growth support and high availability?",
        "choices": [
            "Private WAN",
            "ISP service",
            "SP MPLS/IP VPN",
            "Private MPLS"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "SP MPLS/IP VPN has excellent growth support and high availability",
        "topic": [
            "WAN Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch07.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0071",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "What is NAT-PT?",
        "choices": [
            "Network Address Translation–Port Translation. Translates RFC 1918 addresses to public IPv4 addresses.",
            "Network Addressable Transparent–Port Translation. Translates network addresses to ports.",
            "Network Address Translation–Protocol Translation. Translates between IPv4 and IPv6 addresses.",
            "Next Address Translation–Port Translation."
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "NAT-PT translates between IPv4 and IPv6 addresses",
        "topic": [
            "Internet Protocol Version 6 Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch09.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0075",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which protocol maps names to IPv6 addresses?",
        "choices": [
            "Address Resolution Protocol (ARP)",
            "Network Discovery (ND)",
            "Domain Name System (DNS)",
            "DNSv2"
        ],
        "answer": "C",
        "solution": "The DNS maps fully qualified domain names to IPv6 addresses using (AAAA) records",
        "topic": [
            "Internet Protocol Version 6 Design"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch09.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0127",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which SNMP component contains an agent?",
        "choices": [
            "Managed device",
            "Agent",
            "NMS manager",
            "MIB"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "solution": "Managed devices contain SNMP agents",
        "topic": [
            "Network Management Protocols"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch15.html"
    },
    {
        "id": "9780134305653-A0128",
        "type": 0,
        "question": "Which SNMP component is a collection of information that is stored on the local agent?",
        "choices": [
            "Managed device",
            "Agent",
            "NMS manager",
            "MIB"
        ],
        "answer": "D",
        "solution": "A MIB is a collection of information that is stored on the local agent of the managed device",
        "topic": [
            "Network Management Protocols"
        ],
        "source": "9780134305653/ch15.html"
    }
]